[
	{
		"question": "Where is the Bermuda Triangle located?",
		"options": [
			"Atlantic Ocean",
			"The Arctic Ocean",
			"Pacific Ocean",
			"Indian Ocean"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What is a mass of jellyfish floating together called?",
		"options": [
			"Pack",
			"Flock",
			"Smack",
			"School"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the emitting a bright blue glow the ocean waters?",
		"options": [
			"Bioluminescence",
			"Northern Lights",
			"Biolights",
			"Bio Lights"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the normal lifespan of icebergs?",
		"options": [
			"Less than a year",
			"2-3 years",
			"1-2 years",
			"More than 3 years"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Which is the largest coral reef in the world?",
		"options": [
			"Red Sea Coral Reef",
			"Andros Coral Reef",
			"Florida Reef",
			"Great Barrier Reef"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the primary food source of whales?",
		"options": [
			"Krill",
			"Sharks",
			"Penguins",
			"Starfish"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "\"Carassius auratus\" is the scientific name of which fish?",
		"options": [
			"Blue Whale",
			"Goldfish",
			"Starfish",
			"Red Salmon"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Which is the slowest fish?",
		"options": [
			"Blue Whale",
			"Sailfish",
			"Orca",
			"Seahorse"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What are underwater volcanos called?",
		"options": [
			"Liquid Volcanoes",
			"Submarine Volcanoes",
			"Oceanic Mountains",
			"Sea Peaks"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the most common marine plant?",
		"options": [
			"Asian Surfgrass",
			"Eyelash Seaweed",
			"Red Algae",
			"Green Algae"
		],
		"answer": 3
	}
]